Jon Yeatman

4487 Treeline Court Commerce TWP, MI 48382 404.423.7274 (cell) jonlyeatman@gmail.com

Overview

Experienced Business Owner with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software and graphics industry. Skilled in Business Planning, Operations Management, Web Design, UI/UX, CSS, JavaScript, and Adobe design software. Strong operations professional with a Certificate focused in Full Stack Web Development from Michigan State University.

Experience

Phoenix Custom Printing, LLC Milford, MI 2018 - Present

Founder and owner/operator of a graphic design business specializing in custom artwork for new and returning clients and bringing their ideas to life, maintaining customer relations, prioritizing project scheduling, and creating weekly reports

Superior Edge Leather Works, LLC Milford, MI 2017 – 2019

Specialized in creating custom leather goods as well as standard production items for distribution and online sales; created design templates and mockups for craftsmen to produce individual produce custom products

Michigan Army National Guard, Pontiac, MI 2013 – 2017

Volunteered for service as an Infantryman, responsible for maintaining constant mission readiness and proficiency in a variety of essential military tasks

Mi-Ponderosa, LLC Equestrian Facility and Boarding Stable, South Lyon, MI 2016 – 2017 Served as Ranch Manager, responsible for the care of boarded horses and maintenance of facilities and properties; daily responsibilities included feeding, turning out/in, picking stalls and pastures, filling up nibble nets and water troughs; various tractor and vehicle maintenance; and maintained over 70 acres of property

Golf Course Maintenance, Beacon Hill Golf Club, Commerce TWP, MI 2012 – 2013Worked through junior and senior years of high school, performing golf course care for two 18 hole private golf clubs including operating tractors, mowers and hand-held power equipment

Education

Michigan State University Full Stack Web Development Certificate July 2021

Lakeland High School 2013 (3.5 GPA)

Varsity Football and 2013 Mr. Lakeland Award recipient